MARCH 16, 2006
Chifuyu, I need to Time Leap.
Huh?
I see.
Finally going back 12 years in the future.
Gonna miss you, partner.
It's not that.
I only want to go back a couple of days.
Huh?
It was White Day two days ago!
I was supposed to give Hina her present,
but I totally spaced out and forgot.
She's gonna kill me!
RUMBLE RUMBLE
What do I do, Chifuyu? How do I face Hina?
I'm so screwed!
Put your hands back on the handle bars,
you idiot!
- [crashing]
- [grunting]
Sorry, about that, Chifuyu.
Takemitchy.
Huh?
Even though we missed the actual day,
I think there's a way
that you can save it.
Huh?
It's foolproof.
The Great T2D2 Plan!
"T2D2"?
What is that? Some type of code word?
Let me break it down for you.
It stands for Time Travel and Doki Doki.
THE GREAT TIME TRAVEL DOKI DOKI
T2D2 PLAN.
'Cause it'll make her heart race!
Yeah?
[♪ theme song playing]
[Takemichi] What are these?
- They're love's secret weapon.
- Huh?
The plan is to use these boxes
to set up a dramatic surprise,
to reveal the White Day gift
you forgot to give Hina.
She's going to feel like
the luckiest girl in the world.
That's exactly what I want.
I still don't get it though.
All I see are polka dot boxes,
ribbons and a notebook.
[laughs] Takemitchy,
girls can't resist these things.
Cute little ribbons, polka dot boxes
and big surprises.
I read it in a manga once.
Whoa! I had no idea you were an expert.
MARCH 16
[Chifuyu] The first step is to write dates
on the boxes starting from two days ago.
When she opens them,
you'll also give Hina a note with a clue.
First clue: "You go up me with your feet,
and down me on your butt.
Can you figure out what I am?"
It's a slide, isn't it?
That's correct!
Is your name Einstein or something?
So, when Hina walks over to the slide...
ta-da!
She'll see another box
with March 16th written on it,
which will contain the second clue.
Let's see.
"No matter how long you ride me,
you'll still be stuck in the same place."
Hmm...
The answer's a swing!
Bingo! You're a genius!
So when Hina walks over
to check the swing, what will she see?
The next box with March 15th on it!
Wow! This is amazing, Chifuyu!
It'll be like
we're actually time traveling!
[chuckles]
Ready for the grand finale, Takemitchy.
[grunts]
[Takemichi]
"You won't get hurt if you fall in me,
but you can use what I have inside
to blind someone. What am I?"
Hmm...
Come on.
This is the easiest one.
- There's nothing that I can--
- [footsteps running]
[shouting]
[grunting]
If you wanna win Hina's heart,
you're gonna have to try harder than that!
- It's the sandbox!
- Exactly!
She'll open the last box and be surprised
with your White Day present
and a final message inside that says,
"There was no other day
I could've given this to you"!
You're just like Socrates!
I'm so lucky
that you're my friend, Chifuyu!
- This'll turn everything around!
- Yeah!
Now all I have to do is add the present.
- A ring, huh?
- Yep.
I really hope that Hina likes the design.
Of course she will.
She's gonna love the surprise too.
I think we're ready to start the plan.
Got it!
[gasps] It's game time, Takemitchy.
Hina.
Hey, Takemichi.
Okay, so, maybe I should apologize first,
and then I'll give her the letter?
Crap! I feel like I can't breathe.
- [Hina] I'm sorry.
- Huh?
Why?
Sorry I haven't really been myself.
Between the two of us,
you're probably hurting more than I am.
Huh?
I wish I could hear what they're saying.
Why is Hina bowing like that?
After what happened that day,
I feel like I haven't been the same.
Ever since I saw Kisaki die
right in front of me...
I can still see him.
I keep replaying what happened...
and I'm so scared.
[sobbing]
I can't stop thinking about how Kisaki
and Emma are gone.
What if it was my fault
that they both died?
Hina...
I had no idea what you were going through.
[growls]
What are you saying to her, Takemitchy?
Just stick to the script.
The Great T2D2 Plan is a guarantee.
Have her look under the slide.
[crying]
Hina.
You idiot! The sandbox is the finale!
Hina, here.
A ring?
Yeah.
For White Day. Sorry your gift is late.
What the hell is happening?
Listen, I know I don't have
any special skills,
and I'll probably never get rich.
But I promise...
that taking care of you
and making you happy
will always be my priority.
Hina...
will you please marry me?
[gasps]
- Marry?
- Whenever life gets scary,
I'll be right here to protect you
and keep you safe.
I'm here for you, so please don't cry.
[whimpering]
[clears throat]
Twelve years from now, let's get married.
You two are going to get married?
Quiet down, Naoto!
Do you want the entire world to know?
We're going to wait until we're adults,
of course.
Talk about a spontaneous proposal.
Even my heart's going "doki doki" now.
Thanks for coming here
so last-minute, Naoto.
This is the same park
where we had our first handshake.
It feels right
to have our last one in this place too.
Thank you for everything, Naoto.
I couldn't have done
any of this without you.
I'm only here now because you
and your future self had faith in me.
[gasps] So, does that mean in the future,
that my sister and I were saved?
Yes. Definitely.
It's time. Shake my hand.
Chifuyu. Hina.
See you in the future.
[gasps]
I'm back to the future.
That must mean
that everything worked out!
Naoto must be alive!
Wait a minute.
Why am I in a tux right now?
And where exactly am I?
[tolling]
A tuxedo and bells ringing...
Huh? Could it be...
Let's get married.
[gasps] No way!
[Hina] There you are!
We're going to be late to the reception!
Hina...
After all this time,
it's finally happening.
You can't keep
the man of the hour waiting. Come on!
Who are we talking about?
It's Hayashida's wedding today, remember?
Wait, who's Hayashida?
We need to hurry up!
Hold on! My brain needs to catch up!
My head's about to explode!
[Ken] You're late, Takemitchy.
- Huh?
- Hurry up and sit down.
[MC] And now, the couple of the hour,
please give it up for the bride and groom!
[applause]
So, Hayashida is Pah-chin?
Uh, thank you for joining us.
It's a beautiful day today
with sunny skies and not
a single cloud in sight, and, yeah...
Is this a weather forecast?
You asshole! Don't you know
Pah-chin barely has two brain cells?
He's doing his best!
Peh-yan has always had a way with words.
- [Ryohei] Shut up, Mitsuya!
- Calm down and give it a rest, Peh-yan.
I'm gonna kill all of you
if you guys keep being so loud!
Says the one yelling right now.
Oh, man, Pah-chin's speech
is all over the place.
I guess some things never change.
Right? Takemitchy.
[Pah-chin] The two of us always...
What's up? Are you about to cry?
We're supposed to be happy, Takemichi.
I can't believe that everyone's alive.
Everyone looks so happy.
Smiling and laughing together.
Is everything okay?
Yes, just...
I can't believe we did it.
I'll never forget that day...
Until I can reach the future
where you're finally safe,
I'm never going to quit trying!
I made a promise.
And now you're here...
right in front of me.
[Ryohei] Pretend like it's an enemy.
- Do it in one clean cut.
- Show us how it's done, Pah-chin.
It should be a piece of cake for you.
- Slice it!
- Hurry up!
- Come on!
- We're waiting.
- Do it.
- Shut the hell up!
- [all laughing]
- It's hard to believe, Takemichi.
Huh?
It was 12 years ago today
that you came back here, isn't it?
When I think about it...
it's crazy that the age you were back then
is the exact same age I am right now.
I have been waiting so long
for this day to finally come.
[applauding]
Welcome home, Takemichi.
This isn't a dream, is it, Hina?
Do you want me to pinch you?
[weeping]
I'm not the only one
who's been waiting for you.
It's kind of funny, isn't it?
For us, it's been 12 whole years.
But for you, Takemichi,
we only just said goodbye, didn't we?
You just proposed to Hina at the park too.
That's pretty wild to think about.
I mean, the reason
we're all even alive right now
is because of what you did, Takemitchy.
Chifuyu...
and Draken...
- So thank you for everything.
- So wanna say thanks for everything.
You're incredible, you know that?
Countless lives were saved
because you never gave up.
I couldn't have done it without you guys.
All of you helped me along the way.
What the hell is this?
Why is everyone gettin' all emotional
without me, huh?
Today is supposed to be my day!
You're not considered
the star of the show, you idiot.
The bride is.
You're more like an extra.
- Okay, but I'm still in the show.
- [laughter]
[Chifuyu] Pah-chin took over
his family's business and got rich.
Apparently,
the bride is a childhood friend.
[Ken] Peh-yan's still by Pah-chin's side,
closer than ever.
[Chifuyu] Mitsuya just started out
as a fashion designer,
but he's already making waves.
He even won an award at a big competition.
Amazing.
[Chifuyu] And get this.
Hakkai's a top model now.
- He gets flown out and works overseas.
- [Takemichi] Whoa!
Hey, Taka, hurry up and get on my level
so we can work together.
Your head is getting too big.
[Chifuyu] Yuzuha keeps Hakkai in check
as his manager.
The Kawata brothers traded guns for knives
and run a ramen shop now.
- Really?
- You should come by and try it sometime.
The recipes we've created are killer.
[Ken] And of course,
the shop's name is "Twin Devils."
Wow!
And Kazutora, he's been working
at Chifuyu's shop.
What the hell are you looking at?
You own a shop too?
Well, yeah, but not what you think.
- He runs a pet shop.
- [Takemichi] What?
It's been his dream, right, Matsuno?
We're still pretty small,
but I know we'll get there.
[Takemichi] That's awesome.
- Congrats, Chifuyu.
- [Chifuyu] Thanks.
By the way. Did you order the carburetor
for Takemitchy's bike?
Yeah, it should get here tomorrow.
What? My bike?
Who do you think took care of your bike
for the past 12 years?
Draken partnered up with Inupi,
and they opened up a bike shop together.
Wow. Everyone's doing so well.
[Naoto] Takemichi.
[gasps]
Good to see that you're finally back.
I never doubted you for a second.
Naoto!
You're alive!
Thank God you're actually alive!
Well, of course.
Did you forget that I'm the trigger?
If I was dead,
you wouldn't have made it back here.
Yeah, I know that, but still...
- [sobbing]
- You did it.
Mission accomplished.
This is a future where my sister is alive.
[Takemichi] That's right.
This is the best future by far.
You don't have to worry.
I promise that we until meet again,
I'll protect everyone in Toman,
and I'll keep Hina safe too.
You kept everyone safe,
just like you promised.
Thank you, Mikey.
- Hey, guys?
- Hmm?
Why haven't I seen Mikey yet?
[both chuckle]
Wow! Can you believe that Mikey's
running a business overseas?
He's really doing big things.
They said he works in food,
but I wonder what exactly.
Maybe like a taiyaki chain.
If it is, I bet it's good.
Being too busy to come just proves
that things are going well for him.
Still a bummer, but I get it.
You know,
it's been pretty busy for us too.
Once we have more time,
we have a lot of things to talk about.
Right.
Uh, what do you mean by that?
I mean, this is probably the busiest
the two of us have ever been.
Huh?
Our wedding is in June.
It'll only be three more months
until we get married.
What?
Twelve years felt like forever.
[sighs] Hina.
You've been carrying the weight
of other people's lives for so long,
you deserve to be selfish now.
So, let's make up for it
by living a life full of happiness.
I hope you're ready
for how busy it's gonna get.
We've booked the venue, and we're
already getting close to our budget.
Not to mention
my dress isn't even ready yet.
[whimpers]
I don't know how much happier I can get.
[Takashi] You're a lucky guy, Takemitchy.
Hina haggled so hard with me,
I couldn't get a word in.
So, is this, like, your workshop?
An acquaintance of mine
actually owns the building.
I just rent the attic 'cause it's cheap.
Is that what I think it is?
Is that the wedding dress
that Hina ordered?
Huh?
Yeah, it is. Like it?
- Like it? I love it! It's beautiful.
- [door opens]
Taka, we got what you asked for.
[Takashi] That took a while.
We got mobbed by some fans
as we were leaving,
and this guy froze up again, as always.
Very nice.
- What's this for?
- It's for your tuxedo, Takemitchy.
Stay still. This is a delicate process.
Okay, got it.
Taka's always serious
when it comes to his fittings.
This is where the magic happens, you know?
- Uh... right.
- Wow.
His face is so handsome
when he's all serious.
Shut up, Hakkai. I'm trying to focus.
I'm really proud of how far
you've come, Mitsuya.
You just went independent, and you've
already gotten all these orders.
Yeah, but the work I've been doing
is grunt work.
Arms up.
Oh, right. You fly back to France today.
Go by Twin Devils.
The Ramen's actually good.
I don't really want to eat ramen
made by those psychos.
And I'd rather swing by Chifuyu's place
to see his doggies one more time.
I think I'll stop by Draken's shop
and get him to rev a bike for me.
That always brings back good memories.
Simpler times.
Hmm.
It's wild.
The last thing I tailored for you
was your Toman uniform.
Yeah, I guess it was.
[laughs]
Some things never change, do they?
[laughing]
[Takemichi] It's nice to see that
everyone's still the same
as they were back then.
Have a good day, sir!
I'm still working in the same video store!
Please put DVDs back on the shelf
a soon as they get returned to us,
Mr. Hanagaki.
Right. Sorry.
This place is as filthy as I remember.
But now, I'm happy.
A FEW DAYS LATER
And now an update on the situation
involving the "Bonten" organization.
- This conflict has...
- [Takemichi] Seriously? That's insane.
Well, I guess gangs like Toman
are still around.
...which we believe could help expose
who the core members are.
[Takemichi] That tattoo...
RAMEN - TWIN DEVILS
RAMEN WHITE
Where have I seen that design before?
I can't place my finger on it.
Hey, did you hear anything I just said?
Of course. You were talking
about the wedding dress, right?
Yeah, you're gonna look amazing.
I was talking about the wedding rehearsal!
You need to stop zoning out!
[Souya] Order up.
Wow, it looks great!
So which one is which?
We call the white tonkotsu "Smiley,"
and the black tonkotsu is named "Angry."
The "Angry" is my go-to. Despite the name,
it's got nice subtle flavors.
[slurping]
Spicy!
"Smiley" looks mild,
but it's got a real kick!
Hmm? That photo...
FIRST GENERATION
TOKYO MANJI
[Souya] Oh. That's a commemorative photo
from when Toman disbanded.
[Nahoya] That was the day
I left my whole youth behind.
March 8th, 12 years ago.
I'll never forget it.
All of us should get together
and catch up soon.
It sounds like Mikey's
been doing well for himself.
- Huh? Is that so?
- Well, we wouldn't know.
What? You guys don't meet up with him
when he's back in Japan?
He's running a restaurant overseas, right?
He does?
That's the first I've heard of it.
Huh?
But that's what Draken and Chifuyu said.
I hear ya.
But did they actually see Mikey?
- What?
- We haven't seen Mikey in over ten years.
It's been that long?
Honestly,
I don't think anyone's seen Mikey.
What the heck? What's going on?
- [metallic tinkling]
- [gasps]
Is something wrong?
[tinkling]
[Takemichi] It just hit me.
That design...
is the same one
on Izana Kurokawa's earring!
- Thanks for the food!
- [Hina] Wait! Takemichi?
[panting]
Mikey's overseas.
He got into the food business
and opened up a restaurant.
He's been doing really well over there.
[Takemichi] I don't know why,
but I've got a bad feeling about this!
Draken!
Takemitchy?
Why do you look like you've seen a ghost?
Why did you lie to me, Draken?
The whole thing
about Mikey being overseas...
It's a lie, isn't it?
Smiley and the others said
they haven't seen him in over ten years.
And Mitsuya said
he hasn't seen him either.
And today, as I was watching the news,
I saw someone
who almost looked like Izana Kurokawa.
What if Izana survived that last fight?
What if he's still breathing?
What if he went after Mikey?
BIKER GANG
Izana Kurokawa resented Mikey
until his last breath,
even though Mikey forgave him
for killing Emma.
Don't tell me...
Mikey was killed by Izana?
And here I thought
this was the best future...
Now please tell me the truth.
What really happened to Mikey?
Is he alive?
[♪ theme music playing]
FAIRY TALE REVENGERS
PETIT
- Fairy Tale Revengers.
Hey! Why hasn't my horn grown back yet?
Well, it looks like it snapped off
at the base.
That's gonna take a while to grow back.
[growls]
I'm going to kill that peach bastard.
Hey! Anyone got something
we can use as a horn for now?
ROCK
Way too small. Try again!
FLOWER
What oni wears flowers? Try again!
BUNNY EARS
Do you wanna die?
Forget it.
I'll just break off my horn
and give it to the boss.
If you do that, you'll be hurt too.
But I can't just leave you without a horn.
- I don't need yours.
- You sure?
I'll just rip off a horn
from that bunny-eared dumbass.
[gulping]
Izana!
TO BE CONTINUED